Contact

screer@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sam-creer-mba-bsn-ccrn-13683714 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
CCRN
TNCC
Open Heart Surgery

Sam Creer MBA,BSN,CCRN

Director of Critical Care Services at Kaiser Permanente Atlanta, Georgia

Summary

Experienced Director Of Care with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Critical Care, Hospitals, Life Support, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), and Advanced Trauma Life Support (ATLS). Strong operations professional with a Master of Business Administration - MBA focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from American InterContinental University.

Experience

Kaiser Permanente
3 years 6 months

Director of Critical Care Services

March 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Nursing Supervisor December 2016 - March 2017 (4 months)

Piedmont Healthcare Nursing Supervisor October 2016 - March 2017 (6 months)

Sutter Health
Nursing Supervisor
December 2015 - October 2016 (11 months)
Castro Valley, California

Grady Health System
Sr Staff Charge Nurse ICU/CVICU
August 2005 - December 2015 (10 years 5 months)

West Jefferson Medical Center Critical Care Registered Nurse June 2004 - August 2005 (1 year 3 months)

Education

American InterContinental University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Health/Health Care Administration/

Management

Southern University and Agricultural and Mechanical College at Baton Rouge

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse